hi this video explains when it's a great
idea to use teaching tips to educate
users and what to consider when using
them it's a clip from a launch man video
for 2023 release Wave 2 but it's equally
relevant today let's turn it over to
Sarah will tell us more about
it once users get more Hands-On with the
UI and they try out the scenarios on
their own teaching tips are a valuable
method for educating users about what
they can do in a particular particular
page again when creating content for
these be brief make sure the user
understands the key value of the page as
if you would introduce it in one
sentence to a customer why is this page
so great and not how to use it if users
want to learn more make sure they can
find relevant documentation about your
page in help
instead now if you want users to
discover key elements on a page the tour
with teaching tips are a better choice
because they can point to a particular
action or field and provide an
explanation but remember you can't use
teaching tips to prescribe a certain
business process the sequence of the
teaching tips is controlled by the order
they appear on the page top to bottom
which makes sense because users view
pages from top to bottom and you should
already have arranged your fields in
terms of priority uh from top to
bottom and again sh shorter and fewer
tips is usually better if you try to
communicate too much in these inui
elements you might not get the result
that you intended the users will
typically get tired of balloons and
teaching tips and maybe skip it all
together so narrow it down and think
about the three most important things us
just really need to discover and
understand to learn more visit aka. ms/
BC onboarding thank you for watching
[Music]